ILGWU Western States Region Records 5780/115
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Morris Maler Shirt Manufacturing Company: Arbitration, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Morris Maler Shirt Manufacturing Company: Moore Discharge, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Mode O'Day Company: Arbitration, 1979-1981 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Motif, Incorporated: Arbitration, 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- M. Shapiro Arbitration: Back pay D'Roma, 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Rebuilders: Owens, 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Sav-A-Day Linen: Negotiation, 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Roth Le Cover: Arbitration, Contract Out, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Sierra Lingerie: Negotiations, 1979-1980 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Sierra Lingerie: Negotiations, 1977-1981 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Smart Modes, Incorporated: Trade Readjustment Allowances, 1979-1982 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Smart Modes Incorporated: Cost of Living, 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Smart Modes Incorporated: Benefit Funds, Extra Exhibits, 1973-1982 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- Smart Modes Incorporated: Subpoenas, 1981-1982 (Box 59, Folder 14)
- Smart Modes Incorporated: Arbitration General, 1981-1982 (Box 59, Folder 15)
- Smart Modes Incorporated: Evidence and Notes, 1981-1982 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Smart Modes Incorporated: Exhibits, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Smart Modes Incorporated: Contracts, 1976-1978 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Smart Modes Incorporated: Contracting Out, 1976-1981 (Box 59, Folder 19)
- Smart Modes Incorporated: Holiday Pay, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 20)
- Smart Modes Incorporated: Arbitration, 1979-1981 (Box 59, Folder 21)
- Smart Modes Incorporated: Molina, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 22)
- Smart Modes Incorporated: Inside Shop, 1976-1981 (Box 59, Folder 23)
- Sheperd Manufacturing Company, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- Shepherd Manufacturing Company: Grievances, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 25)
- Southern California Davis Pleating Company, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 26)
- Southern California Davis Pleating Company: Arbitration, 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 27)
- Scott, Maria, 1979-1980 (Box 59, Folder 28)
- Sav-A-Day Linen Service: Soto, Jose, 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 29)
- Standard Swiss: Suppliers (Box 59, Folder 30)
- Vita Coats, Incorporated: Wage Rate Arbitration, 1979-1981 (Box 59, Folder 31)
- Armak and Company v. Los Angeles Joint Board1, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Loya Aurora v. ILGWU, 1982-1983 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Ben Fish v. ILGWU: Wall, 1979-1982 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Buchanan, J. v. ILGWU: Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1977-1982 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Solomon v. Bel Air Belt Company, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Los Angeles Joint Board v. Cappr Originals, 1974-1982 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Fekete v. Reyes, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Fisher Dress Company: ILGWU, 1978-1979 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- International Knits, Incorporated, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Los Angeles Joint Board v. International Knits, Incorporated, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Freeman v. ILGWU, 1979-1980 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Gonzalez, Jesus R: Death Benefit Inquiry, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Jo Lene Company, Incorporated: Negotiations, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Levy, Robert v. ILGW Federal Credit Union, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Main on Foods Corporation: Employment Development Department Unemployment Inquiry, Trade Dispute, 1976-1983 (Box 60, Folder 15)
- M. Shapiro and Company, 1979-1980 (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Nelson, Inez v. ILGWU: Holly Stores, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Motif, Incorporated, 1978-1982 (Box 60, Folder 18)
- Motif, Incorporated: Assignment to Credit and Claims, 1982-1983 (Box 60, Folder 19)
- Nicholas v. Diaz: ILGWU [folder 1 of 3], 1977-1984 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Nicholas v. Diaz: ILGWU [folder 2 of 3], 1977-1984 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Nicholas v. Diaz: ILGWU [folder 3 of 3], 1977-1984 (Box 60, Folder 22)
- Standard Swiss Embroidery Corporation: Injunction, 1980-1981 (Box 60, Folder 23)
- Standard Swiss Embroidery Corporation: Injunction #2, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Starline Coat Company of California: ILGWU, 1977-1980 (Box 60, Folder 25)
- Park Pleating Company, 1980-1984 (Box 60, Folder 26)
- ILGWU: M. Shapiro and Company, 1976-1979 (Box 60, Folder 27)
- Southern California District Council: Annetta of California, 1979-1981 (Box 60, Folder 28)
- Reyes v. Hill, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 29)
- Sanchez, Richardo Garcia: Standard Swiss Embroidery Corporation, 1980-1981 (Box 60, Folder 30)
- Solis, Laura v. ILGWU, 1982-1983 (Box 60, Folder 31)
- Southern California Davis Pleating v. ILGWU National Retirement Fund, 1983-1984 (Box 60, Folder 32)
- ILGWU Los Angeles Joint Board v. Smart Maid Garment Company, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Southern California Davis Pleating Company: Arbitration, 1980-1982 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Southern California Davis Pleating Company: Arbitration, 1979-1982 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Local 512: Warehouse and Office Workers Union, 1979-1981 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- ILGWU v. Rothschild of California: Bankruptcy Claim, 1978-1983 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Fred Rothschild of California, 1974-1983 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Bruno D'Anna: Los Angeles Joint Board, ILGWU, 1977-1981 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Los Angeles Joint Board v. Annetta of California, 1976-1981 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- ILGWU v. Annetta of California: Extra Briefs, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Los Angeles Joint Board, ILGWU v. D'Anna Garment Company, 1973-1981 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Los Angeles Joint Board v. Annetta of California, 1978-1980 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Los Angeles Joint Board v. Annetta of California, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Labor Relations Report [folder 1 of 2], 1981-1983 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Labor Relations Report [folder 1 of 2], 1981-1983 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Justice, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  French
- The Los Angeles Citizen: News, 1981-1982 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Memorandums, 1981-1982 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- California AFL-CIO News, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Apparel News, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO News, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Fairchild's Textile and Apparel Financial Directory, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- California AFL-CIO News, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- California Apparel News, 1981-1983 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- State Senate Campaigns, 1973-1974 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- ILGWU Convention, 1976-1977 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- California AFL-CIO News, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- ALF-CIO Newspaper, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Board of Directors, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- ILGWU: Employment, 1961-1973 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Labor Union Committees, 1974-1975 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- California Labor Federation AFL-CIO, 1976-1980 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- ILGWU: Election Results, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- California Labor Federation AFL-CIO: Convention [folder 1 of 2], 1968-1976 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- California Labor Federation AFL-CIO: Convention [folder 2 of 2], 1968-1976 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Frank-Lee of California: Cutting and Cost Analysis, 1971-1973 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Allied Auto Parks, Incorporated, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union AFL-CIO, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- American Trade Union Council: Histadrut, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Appleton, Shelley: Correspondence, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Arizona-Utah District Council: Correspondence, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Assembly Bills, 1975-1978 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Arizona State AFL-CIO: Correspondence, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Athlone Industries, Incorporated, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Audit Notes, 1975-1982 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Bay Area, ILGWU Welfare Fund: Correspondence, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Bonanno, Nick: Director Southeast Region, ILGWU, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Edmund G Brown Jr, Governor: Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- California AFL-CIO News, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- California Conference on Immigration and Public Policy, 1976-1978 (Box 64, Folder 14)
- California Democratic Party, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 15)
- California Health Facilities Commission, 1979-1980 (Box 64, Folder 16)
- California Labor Federation: AFL-CIO, 1979-1980 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Cal-Mart Travel Service, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Cambodia Crisis Fund-Raising, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 19)
- Canada, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 20)
- Cedar-Sinai Medical Center, 1978-1979 (Box 64, Folder 21)
- Central Labor Council of San Bernardino and Riverside County, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 22)
- Central State Region: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 64, Folder 23)
- Certified Public Accounts, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 24)
- Chaikin, Sol C: President, 1977-1980 (Box 64, Folder 25)
- Chairmen, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 26)
- Check-Off Authorization for Political Contributions, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 27)
- Chinese Hospital, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 28)
- Christmas Materials, 1972-1980 (Box 64, Folder 29)
- The Citizen: Los Angeles, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 30)
- City of Hope, 1977-1980 (Box 64, Folder 31)
- City of Los Angeles, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 32)
- Civil Rights, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 33)
- Coat and Suit Contractors Association: Back Pay Case, 1976-1979 (Box 64, Folder 34)
- Committee on Political Education: ALF-CIO, 1978-1979 (Box 64, Folder 35)
- Community Networker, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 36)
- Community Relations Conference, 1978-1980 (Box 64, Folder 37)
- Consumer Price Watch, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 38)
- Contract Expiration Notices: Sent out, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 39)
- Contract Negotiations: Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 64, Folder 40)
- ILGWU: 1977 Convention (Box 64, Folder 41)
- ILGWU: Convention Resolutions, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 42)
- Cost of Living Bulletins, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 43)
- Credit Card Applications: Restaurants, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 44)
- Danahy, Joseph: ILGWU, N.Y., 1979 (Box 64, Folder 45)
- Daniels, Wilbur: Executive Vice-President, 1976-1980 (Box 64, Folder 46)
- Diaz v. Nicholas, 1978-1980 (Box 64, Folder 47)
- District Councils Merger Forms (Box 64, Folder 48)
- Division of Industrial Accidents, 1968-1970 (Box 64, Folder 49)
- Division of Labor Statistics and Research, 1977-1980 (Box 64, Folder 50)
- Dock, Larry: Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 64, Folder 51)
- Donations, 1978-1979 (Box 64, Folder 52)
- Dubrow, Evelyn: Political Department, 1978-1980 (Box 64, Folder 53)
- Dues, Rates and Assessments, 1972-1980 (Box 64, Folder 54)
- Dunn and Bradstreet Reports, 1977-1979 (Box 64, Folder 55)
- National Labor Relations Board: Bouquets Fashions, 1978-1979 (Box 64, Folder 56)
- Feinberg, Basil, 1975-1981 (Box 64, Folder 57)
- Financial Statements: Bay Area, ILGWU Employer's Health and Welfare Fund, 1979-1980 (Box 64, Folder 58)
- Financial Statements: Arizona-Utah District Council, Schedule of Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1977-1979 (Box 64, Folder 59)
- Financial Statements: Bay Area, ILGWU Vacation Fund, 1974-1980 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- ILGWU: Employer Vacation. Health and Welfare Statement of Assets and Liability, 1979-1980 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Financial Statements: ILGWU Health Service Plan, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Financial Statements: ILGWU National Retirement Fund, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Portland, Oregon: Local 70, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Seattle, Washington: Local 184, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Local 270, 1974-1978 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Local 271, 1972-1978 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Local 277, 1974-1978 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Local 278, 1974-1978 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Local 289, 1974-1978 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Local 293, 1971-1978 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Local 294, 1972-1978 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Local 385, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Local 430, 1974-1978 (Box 65, Folder 15)
- Financial Statements: ILGWU San Francisco Joint Board, Statement of Receipts and Disbursements, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 16)
- Local 451, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 17)
- Local 497, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 18)
- Southern California District Council: Subordinate Accounts, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 19)
- Financial Statements: Western States Region, ILGWU Administration Fund, 1977-1978 (Box 65, Folder 20)
- Financial Statements: Western State Region, Benefit Fund Status, 1978-1979 (Box 65, Folder 21)
- Financial Statements: Western States Region, ILGWU Subordinate Accounts Summary of Cash Transaction, 1975-1979 (Box 65, Folder 22)
- Fines for Missing Local Meetings, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 23)
- Garcia, Mendoza and Martinez: Attorneys at Law, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 24)
- General Executive Board, 1979-1980 (Box 65, Folder 25)
- General Executive Board [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1980 (Box 65, Folder 26)
- General Executive Board [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1980 (Box 65, Folder 27)
- Gas Cards: Mobil, Arco, Chevron, 1976-1977 (Box 65, Folder 28)
- Golden Club ILGWU: Los Angeles, 1976-1980 (Box 65, Folder 29)
- Greenstone, Ellen S., 1980 (Box 65, Folder 30)
- Grievance Committee, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 31)
- Hardaway, Audrey, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 32)
- Hertz: Correspondence, 1977-1982 (Box 65, Folder 33)
- Hertz: Automobile Insurance, 1976-1981 (Box 65, Folder 34)
- Holiday and Vacation Policy, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 35)
- ILGWU: Archives, 1979-1980 (Box 65, Folder 36)
- ILGWU California Building Corporation, 1979-1980 (Box 65, Folder 37)
- ILGWU Building Corporation: Los Angeles Cloak Joint Board, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 38)
- ILGWU: Campaign Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 65, Folder 39)
- ILGWU: Collection Control Department, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 40)
- ILGWU: Education Department, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 41)
- ILGWU Election and Instructions: Northwest Pacific, 1976-1980 (Box 65, Folder 42)
- ILGWU: Election and Objection Committee, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 43)
- ILGWU Newspaper, 1979-1980 (Box 65, Folder 44)
- ILGWU: Research Department, 1978-1980 (Box 65, Folder 45)
- Ideal Pleating and Stitching Company, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Ideal Pleating and Stitching Company, 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Ideal Pleating and Stitching Company, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Jean Pier: California Sewing, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Valle Verde, Incorporated, 1979-1983 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Glydon's, Incorporated, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Glydon, Incorporated: Employee Lists, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Grunwelle-Marx (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Glydon, Incorporated: Settlement, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- ILGWU: Local 512, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Hollywood Bed and Spring Manufacturing Company, Incorporated, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Hollander Home Fashions Corporation, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Hollander Home Fashions Corporation, 1978-1979 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Ideal Pleating and Stitching Company [Folder 1 of 3], 1980 (Box 66, Folder 14)
- Ideal Pleating and Stitching Company [Folder 2 of 3], 1980 (Box 66, Folder 15)
- Ideal Pleating and Stitching Company [Folder 3 of 3], 1980 (Box 66, Folder 16)
- Glydon's, Incorporated [folder 1 of 4], 1980 (Box 66, Folder 17)
- Glydon's, Incorporated [folder 1 of 3], 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 18)
- Glydon's, Incorporated: Exhibits, 1981-1982 (Box 66, Folder 19)
- Glydon's, Incorporated: Settlement Release, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 20)
- Glydon's, Incorporated, 1981-1982 (Box 66, Folder 21)
- Glydon's, Incorporated: Questionnaire, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 22)
- Glydon's, Incorporated: Witnesses, Trial, 1979-1981 (Box 66, Folder 23)
- Glydon's, Incorporated [folder 2 of 3], 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 24)
- ILGWU: Glydon's, Incorporated, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 25)
- Glydon's, Incorporated [folder 3 of 3], 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 26)
- Glydon's, Incorporated [folder 2 of 4], 1980 (Box 66, Folder 27)
- Glydon's, Incorporated [folder 3 of 4], 1980 (Box 66, Folder 28)
- Glydon's, Incorporated [folder 4 of 4], 1980 (Box 66, Folder 29)
- Glydon's, Incorporated: Witnesses, 1979-1980 (Box 66, Folder 30)
- Glydon's, Incorporated, 1979-1980 (Box 66, Folder 31)
- Glydon's, Incorporated, 1982-1983 (Box 66, Folder 32)
- San Rae Sportswear, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Sav-A-Day Linen Service, 1979-1980 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Sav-A-Day Linen Service, 1979-1980 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Sav-A-Day Linen Service, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Sav-A-Day Linen Service, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Sav-A-Day Textile, 1979-1980 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Seven-Up Bottling Company, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Shepherd Manufacturing Company, 1979-1980 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Shepherd Manufacturing Company, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Shepherd Manufacturing Company, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Shepherd Manufacturing Company, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Shepherd Manufacturing Company, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 12)
- Shepherd Manufacturing Company, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 13)
- Shepherd Manufacturing Company, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 14)
- Sherry Fran Knitting Mills, Incorporated, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder 15)
- Sierra Lingerie, 1979-1980 (Box 67, Folder 16)
- Sierra Lingerie, 1979-1980 (Box 67, Folder 17)
- Sierra Lingerie, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 18)
- Southern California-Davis Industries, 1969-1978 (Box 67, Folder 19)
- Southern California-Davis Pleating Company, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 20)
- Southern California-Davis Pleating Company, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 21)
- Southern California-Davis Pleating Company, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 22)
- Southern California-Davis Pleating Company, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 23)
- Southern California District Council, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 24)
- Southern California District Council: ILGWU, 1983-1984 (Box 67, Folder 25)
- Southern California District Council, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 26)
- Southern California District Council, 1981-1982 (Box 67, Folder 27)
- Southern California District Council, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 28)
- Southern California District Council, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 29)
- Southern California District Council: ILGWU, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 30)
- Spring City: Glendale Letter, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 31)
- Spring City Knitting, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 32)
- Standard Swiss Embroidery Corporation, 1980-1981 (Box 67, Folder 33)
- Standard Swiss Embroidery Corporation, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 34)
- Standard Swiss Embroidery Corporation: Jerry Castle, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 35)
- Stitchcraft, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 36)
- Stitching and Pleating, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 37)
- Stual, Incorporated: Maricella, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 38)
- Style Craft Shirt and Blouse Company, Incorporated, 1978-1979 (Box 67, Folder 39)
- Sun-Cal Coats and Jackets Manufacturers, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 40)
- Sun-Cal Coats and Jackets Manufacturers: Records, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 41)
- Sun-Cal Coats and Jackets Manufacturers: Plant Closure, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 42)
- Superior Pleating and Stitching Company, Incorporated, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 43)
- Swan of California, Incorporated, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder 44)
- Tanne Apparel, Incorporated, 1975-1977 (Box 67, Folder 45)
- Avalos, Jose: E. Strauss Arbitration, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Anjac Fashions: Request for Information, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- The Fels Company: Benefit Fund Delinquencies, 1978-1982 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Glydon's, Incorporated: Vacation Grievance, 1981-1983 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Swartz, Harold: Audit, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Hedman Hedders: Benefit Fund Dispute, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- HRT Industries, Incorporated: Sale of Shoe Stop, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- LC Mae of Hollywood, Incorporated: Contracting-Out, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- ILGWU National Retirement Fund v. Lorrie Deb Corporation, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- Manny Industries: Holiday Pay, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 10)
- Manny Industries: Report Pay, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- Main on Foods: Jaime Torres, Discharge Grievances, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 12)
- Morris Maler: Dues Problem, 1982-1984 (Box 68, Folder 13)
- Main on Foods: Delgado Arbitration, 1984-1985 (Box 68, Folder 14)
- Delgado, Gladys: Insurance Grievance, 1983-1984 (Box 68, Folder 15)
- Mercado v. ILGWU: Workers Compensation Appeals Board, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 16)
- Mutual Industries, Incorporated: Arbitration, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 17)
- PRC Recording Company: Negative Shutdown, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 18)
- Rayson Casting and Manufacturing: Benefit Dues, 1979-1984 (Box 68, Folder 19)
- Sir James, Incorporated: Contracting Out, Arbitration, 1978-1985 (Box 68, Folder 20)
- Stual Manufacturing Company, Incorporated: Contracting Out and Holiday Pay Grievances, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 21)
- Southern California-Davis Pleating: Negative, 1983-1984 (Box 68, Folder 22)
- Southern California-Davis Pleating: California Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board, 1983-1984 (Box 68, Folder 23)
- Southern California-Davis Pleating: Negotiation File, 1983-1984 (Box 68, Folder 24)
- Southern California-Davis Pleating: Negotiation File, 1983-1984 (Box 68, Folder 25)
- Southern California-Davis Pleating: Contacts with Jobbers, 1983-1984 (Box 68, Folder 26)
- Southern California-Davis Pleating: Picketing/ Concrete Problem, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 27)
- Southern California-Davis Pleating: Advertisement, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 28)
- Southern California-Davis Pleating: Strike, Jerell, Incorporated, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 29)
- Southern California-Davis Pleating: H and W Audit Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 68, Folder 30)
- Southern California-Davis Pleating: Press Conference, 1983-1984 (Box 68, Folder 31)
- Southern California-Davis Pleating: Strike Sanctions, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 32)
- Southern California-Davis Pleating: Contracting Out, 1982-1984 (Box 68, Folder 33)
- Stual Manufacturing Company, Incorporated: Transfer of Interest Notice, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 34)
- Southern California-Davis Pleating:: Alvarado v. Parks, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 35)
- Solis v. ILGWU, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 36)
- Standard Swiss Embroidery Corporation, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 37)
- Long, Steve, 1980-1981 (Box 68, Folder 38)
- Luna, Lenora, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 39)
- Leiva, Maria Salinas, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 40)
- Lima, Carmen, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 41)
- Francisca Martinez, Ana Butanda, Carmen Gutierrez, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 42)
- City Attorney: Arraignments, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 43)
- Bourque, Suzanne, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 44)
- Palacio, Jaime: MOTIF, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 45)
- Silva, Danny/ Reyes, Cesar, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 46)
- Quintero, Gabina: Mona Lee, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 47)
- Romero, Amelia: Armak, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 48)
- Franco, Carlos: Claim For Wages Due, 1979-1980 (Box 68, Folder 49)
- Van Pattern Company, Incorporated: Arbitration, Vacation Pay Grievance, 1983-1984 (Box 68, Folder 50)
- Van Pattern Company, Incorporated: Medical/ Access, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 51)
- Ortiz, Maria Socorro: False Arrest, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 52)
- Pleitez, Mercedez Police Reports and City Attorney Reports, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 53)
- Marin, Juan and Cisneros, Felipe, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 54)
- Pendleton: Standard Swiss Embroidery Corporation, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 55)
- Standard Swiss Embroidery Corporation: Ramos, Rosio F., 1981 (Box 68, Folder 56)
- Mendez, Luz: Standard Swiss Embroidery Corporation, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 57)
- Castillo, Luz Maria, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 58)
- LeBeau Emblem: Criminal, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 59)
- Flores, Jesus, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 60)
- ILGWU: LeBeau Emblem Company [folder 1 of 2], 1981 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- ILGWU: LeBeau Emblem Company [folder 2 of 2], 1981 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Southern California Cooperative Warehouse, Incorporated: Negotiations, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Valle, Luis v. Southern California-Davis Pleating, 1980-1983 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Cortez, Luis Sanchez, 1980-1981 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Salgado-Reyes, Jesus, 1979-1982 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Menjiba-Mejia, Carlos, 1979-1981 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Pantoja-Mercado, Alberto, 1979-1983 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Gonzalez-Barajas, Maria, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Padilla-Renteria, Dionicio, 1979-1981 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Sosa, Enrique, 1979-1981 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- Ganal-Soto, Francisco, 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Vera-Verde, Amancio, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Leiva-Galenana, Roberta, 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 14)
- Regalado, Hilda Virginia, 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 15)
- Lopez-Orozco, Liliana, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 16)
- Calderon-Urena, Maria, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 17)
- Aguiano-Gonzalez, David, 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 18)
- Diaz-Ibarra, Ramon, 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 19)
- Miranda-Ortega, Sofia, 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 20)